<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Brandon Giesing</title><description>Ramblings About Stuff</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><image><url>http://localhost:2368/favicon.png</url><title>Brandon Giesing</title><link>http://localhost:2368/</link></image><generator>Ghost 1.5</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 02:56:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>No Love In This Timeline | Glitchtale Season 2</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://vid.me/e/gjXp?stats=1" width="100%" height="100%" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For once, nobody died! I applaud you Camila for holding back this one episode! Then again, it is only Part 1 so if Part 2 has deaths I guess someone did die, in that case, NotLikeThis Camila!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="credits"&gt;CREDITS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id="music"&gt;MUSIC&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Undying - NyxTheShield (from Glitchtale OST)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="clips"&gt;CLIPS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Glitchtale S2 E4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/06/29/glitchtale-love-shorties/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">598e673cf9f83b66e1d616bc</guid><category>CosiCast Shorties</category><category>CosiCast</category><category>Glitchtale</category><dc:creator>Brandon Giesing</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 13:49:53 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/love.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://vid.me/e/gjXp?stats=1" width="100%" height="100%" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/love.jpg" alt="No Love In This Timeline | Glitchtale Season 2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;For once, nobody died! I applaud you Camila for holding back this one episode! Then again, it is only Part 1 so if Part 2 has deaths I guess someone did die, in that case, NotLikeThis Camila!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="credits"&gt;CREDITS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id="music"&gt;MUSIC&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Undying - NyxTheShield (from Glitchtale OST)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="clips"&gt;CLIPS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Glitchtale S2 E4 - Love (Part 1)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="outromusic"&gt;OUTRO MUSIC&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Energy - Michael Craig &amp;amp; Oliver Godfrey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="checkoutcamilaandtheglitchtalecastcrew"&gt;CHECK OUT CAMILA AND THE GLITCHTALE CAST/CREW&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/CamiAnimations/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/CamiAnimations/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
DeviantArt: &lt;a href="http://camilaanims.deviantart.com/"&gt;http://camilaanims.deviantart.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Tumblr: &lt;a href="http://camilaart.tumblr.com/"&gt;http://camilaart.tumblr.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Twitter: @camilacuevaszu&lt;br&gt;
Twitch: &lt;a href="https://www.twitch.tv/camila2929"&gt;https://www.twitch.tv/camila2929&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Patreon: &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/camilacuevas"&gt;https://www.patreon.com/camilacuevas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strelok (Sound Designer &amp;amp; Asgore/Frisk/Kumu) - &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/carmelo580"&gt;https://youtube.com/carmelo580&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Zedrin (Sans/Gaster) - &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/ZombieZephyr"&gt;https://youtube.com/ZombieZephyr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Courtney (Betty) - &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/ProjectSNT"&gt;https://youtube.com/ProjectSNT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Jen (Jessica/Orange girl: Robin) - &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/MEMJ0123"&gt;https://youtube.com/MEMJ0123&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Adox0graphist (Asriel/Undyne) - &lt;a href="https://adoxtalks.tumblr.com/"&gt;https://adoxtalks.tumblr.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Lumisau (Green boy: Cam) - &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/lumisau"&gt;https://soundcloud.com/lumisau&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Meredith (Light-Blue Girl: Abigail): &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/Emichwan88"&gt;https://youtube.com/Emichwan88&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
KateMarie999 (Alphys) - &lt;a href="https://katemarie999.tumblr.com/"&gt;https://katemarie999.tumblr.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Citrus (Papyrus) &lt;a href="https://citrusstorm.tumblr.com/"&gt;https://citrusstorm.tumblr.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Casting to new heights! | Big CosiCast Update!</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://vid.me/e/mrP1?stats=1" width="100%" height="100%" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CosiCast is getting a major overhaul with some &lt;strong&gt;HUGE&lt;/strong&gt; changes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="redefiningcurrentshows"&gt;Redefining Current Shows&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end of last year, I made some changes to CosiCast to divide my content up into Shows based on the content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These included:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shorties: Short random videos covering a range of things from music edits&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/06/27/casting-to-new-heights-big-cosicast-update-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">598e673cf9f83b66e1d616bb</guid><category>announcements</category><category>CosiCast</category><dc:creator>Brandon Giesing</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 14:52:43 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/cosicast-changes.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://vid.me/e/mrP1?stats=1" width="100%" height="100%" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/cosicast-changes.jpg" alt="Casting to new heights! | Big CosiCast Update!"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CosiCast is getting a major overhaul with some &lt;strong&gt;HUGE&lt;/strong&gt; changes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="redefiningcurrentshows"&gt;Redefining Current Shows&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end of last year, I made some changes to CosiCast to divide my content up into Shows based on the content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These included:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shorties: Short random videos covering a range of things from music edits to memes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In 60 Seconds: A topic presented at a fast pace, visual only way! No text or talking, only images, videos, and music!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promo Promotions: Fan ads to promote Internet creators from YouTube, Twitch, and more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fan Music Videos (aka FMVs): Music edits based on a topic or specific fandom using a full-length song.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might have noticed here recently that I've done a lot of Shorties, very few In 60 Seconds and FMVs, and no new Promo Promotions... You also might have noticed that each type is very similar and doesn't have that clear of a divide. Today I'm making some changes to simplify and enhance them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="shortiesin60seconds"&gt;Shorties/In 60 Seconds&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shorties are going to stay mostly the same as it is now since it's pretty clear what it is and I do a lot of them. However, In 60 Seconds is gonna be merged into Shorties as most of them weren't exactly 60 seconds and Shorties are also usually about only 1 topic anyway as is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The big difference here is actually a return of some older stuff! I used to do more of the funny meme ones (like the Gravity Falls/Nostalgia Critic thing if you remember that) but now it's all been music mashups basically. I'm going to try and do more of the meme ones but don't worry, music ones are still going to happen and they are likely going to be the majority still.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="fanmusicvideosfmvs"&gt;Fan Music Videos (FMVs)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These are also going to be staying mostly the same as before with 2 big differences:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Like Promo Promotions, I'm gonna be changing the Outro for these. Since they are Music Videos, I'm going to let the end of the music play over the outro instead of my normal Outro Music so it's not as jarring and they can be listened to like normal music videos which usually end when the song does.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;These are now going to be Vidme Exclusives! A big reason for this is since these rely on a full song, they are a lot more prone to DMCA/Music ID stuff than the small clips used in other videos. Also by moving these to Vidme, I can also open it up to more songs as I previously tried to only use royalty-free music for these because of the DMCA crap.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="promopromotions"&gt;Promo Promotions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The changes to Promo Promotions are going to be a bit later down in the post. You'll see why shortly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="recap"&gt;Recap&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So to recap all the changes above:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shorties stay mostly the same but brings back more meme-like ones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In 60 Seconds is discontinued becomes a part of Shorties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fan Music Videos stay mostly the same and are becoming Vidme Exclusive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep reading for Promo Promotions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="newshows"&gt;New Shows!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to the changes to the existing shows to streamline them, I'm introducing two new shows!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="cosiconversations"&gt;Cosi Conversations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So do you remember back in April 2016 when I uploaded Episode 1 of a new series called &amp;quot;The Weekly Prime&amp;quot; before I even made the above 4 shows and that I never uploaded an episode 2 even though the show was supposed to be weekly? Do you also remember Casting With Cosi which I launched in March and then basically did the same thing? Yeah... so I kinda failed on that one!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, I'm bringing both back and merging them into a new show called Cosi Conversations! Like CWC, it's going to be a full-on variety show instead of a fast-paced video with 5 topics like TWP. However, unlike CWC and like TWP, it's going to be video and audio instead of audio-only.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what is the show going to be like? It's going to be a 30 minute to 1-hour program divided into the following segments:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Prime:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I'm reprising the role of The Weekly Prime as a quick top 5 of my fave topics since the last episode inside of Cosi Conversations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basically going to be the same format as before but of course, with the addition of my voice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep Discussions
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I'm going to provide more detail and discuss a topic or two (could be one from The Prime or not)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creator Casting
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Showcasing new shows/videos/songs/channels/etc I like.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TechHouse
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reviving my TechHouse brand I had a long time ago for a segment about Technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May include some sub-segments for Tutorials, Tips, news, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cosi's Corner
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basically your standard fan mailbag segment. I'll answer questions and stuff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you have made fan-work of the channel mascot Cosi, I'll show it off also.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not every episode is going to include every segment of course and they can change in the future. Also, the show is going to be scripted unlike past shows to prevent rambling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The show will always have at least one episode a month but may also have more. This way, I'm not locked into a tight weekly schedule that is easy to miss but I also don't go months on end without posting it effectively canceling it. Audio versions will be on Anchor and SoundCloud while Video versions will be Vidme Exclusive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="cosicommentary"&gt;Cosi Commentary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obviously, by now, everyone has seen Reaction videos where people watch a video and well, react to what they saw. Cosi Commentary is a twist on the standard reaction concept! Not only will I be watching the video and giving my first &amp;quot;blind&amp;quot; reaction to it like normal reactions but I'll then go back and analyze, theorize, and discuss the video in depth to provide my overall thoughts on the video and I'll give it a rating of how much I liked it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like Cosi Conversations above, these are also going to be Vidme Exclusives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="castchannel"&gt;CAST Channel&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now time for the biggest announcement of them all, Pravox VARIETY is coming back as CAST Channel! Like before, CAST Channel is going to be a linear web-based TV channel but with some changes to not only make it easier for me to manage but also more varied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/cast-channel.jpg" alt="Casting to new heights! | Big CosiCast Update!"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="shows"&gt;Shows&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of relying on YouTube Videos and all user submissions, I'm going to make edit together blocks of programs. The big advantage of this is I can make perfectly curated shows that I can replay exactly and schedule better. For comparison, the old style meant I had to add 30+ videos into a block and it played all the videos I added in a row making each block easily over 2 hours. I had to do this otherwise the channel would run out of content but it made it near impossible to manage as to replace the videos with fresh content, I had to completely delete the block which would also change the order it played.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I'll be able to tightly pack stuff into neat 30-60 minute videos with &amp;quot;ad breaks&amp;quot; (more on this later) and be able to put a channel bug in the corner which I couldn't do before at all. While this might take a bit longer to set up as I actually have to edit the videos together, it allows me to reuse full blocks! This means I can do encore airings and throw a past episode up if I need more time to complete the new one. Videos will be mostly picked by me and some others I talk with but there will be Viewer Submission Blocks which will contain videos viewers submit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Current shows are to be determined (TBD) but you can expect Pravox PRESENTS (now CAST Presents), Pravox TUNE (CAST Tune) and Pravox TECH (CAST TechHouse) to come back and for the two new CosiCast shows to be a part of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="adbreaks"&gt;Ad Breaks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So you know I mentioned above to keep reading for more info on Promo Promotions? Well, they are going to be a part of CAST alongside some other stuff in the ad breaks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each break will include a few retro ads, CAST Bumpers, and CAST Promos. &lt;strong&gt;CAST will not include any actually paid ads!!&lt;/strong&gt; This is of course cause I'm playing others content of course and don't want to monetize it. The retro ads are included for fun basically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="castpromos"&gt;CAST Promos&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CAST Promos are going to be like a mix of Promo Promotions and the previous Pravox VARIETY Presents ads with some additional changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the Pravox format:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They will always start and end with the CAST logo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They will use songs non-specific to the creator but unlike the old Pravox ones, it won't always be Checkpoint by Nitro Fun but a select few songs. So not everyone will share the same song like Pravox but also not each video will have a unique song per creator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Links to CAST website and Social Media.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the Promo Promotions format:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being divided up into sections based on their content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Featuring Creator Info like Website and Social Media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And some new things:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Voice-over&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower-third during the full video showing who the creator is at all times.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sometimes, might include voice clips of the person.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I'm opening it up to more than just &amp;quot;creators&amp;quot;. Now, anything I want to make a trailer for basically. Some will be promos for actual things airing on CAST, others will be for creators, some might be for games, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For promos that are about stuff airing, they will include the times they air.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="recap"&gt;Recap&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pravox VARIETY is back as CAST Channel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More professional now with legit voice-overs, promos, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Going to make actual edited shows
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pravox PRESENTS, TUNE, and TECH are coming back&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The two new CosiCast shows will be included.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ad Breaks that include fun retro ads but no actual paid ads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CAST Promos are a merge of the old Promo Promotions and VARIETY ads with some new tweaks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CAST Channel isn't ready yet so make sure to check back here or follow me on social media for more info!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="finalrecap"&gt;Final Recap&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simplifying existing shows by merging Shorties and In 60 Seconds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Making two new shows which are going to be the first on-camera shows by me&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reviving Pravox VARIETY as CAST Channel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So CosiCast is expanding a lot!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>More, More, More, and most importantly, MORE! | Updates &amp; Stuff #3</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another week and more updates! This week's focus is doing more of various things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="supportmepageupdated"&gt;Support Me Page Updated!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you love what I do, it would be really nice if you helped me to make more! That's why I have a page with ways you guys can help me continue&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/06/27/updates-3/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">598e673cf9f83b66e1d616b8</guid><category>Updates &amp; Stuff</category><category>announcements</category><dc:creator>Brandon Giesing</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 11:28:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another week and more updates! This week's focus is doing more of various things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="supportmepageupdated"&gt;Support Me Page Updated!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you love what I do, it would be really nice if you helped me to make more! That's why I have a page with ways you guys can help me continue to do what I do. A lot of the options don't even require you to have to spend money to do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I currently have many different kind of ways to help me on my support page:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct Cash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Things like getting donations via PayPal, Cryptocurrencies, or tips/subscriptions on Vidme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I get cash directly and then buy anything I want to focus on with it)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start="2"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commissions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you buy stuff on my Store page, click the ads on the site, or view &lt;a href="http://Shorte.st"&gt;Shorte.st&lt;/a&gt; links.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also includes Money Routine Referral Links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start="3"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Merch/Products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Physical items you can buy I made like my Bandcamp music, RedBubble stickers/shirts/mugs/etc, and my Wallpaper Collection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start="4"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gifts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All of the above give me money to spend on stuff but you also can just buy the stuff directly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My Amazon Wishlist is the big example here. You buy the stuff with your Amazon account and it gets shipped to me.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start="5"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feedback/&amp;quot;Spread the Word&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lastly, if you have no money you can always just let me know how to improve and tell others to check out my stuff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've added some new things and updated the layout of everything!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="newmethodssitefunddonationsandmorecrypto"&gt;New Methods: Site Fund Donations and more Crypto!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today's first new method is a &amp;quot;Gifts&amp;quot; one. Do you like what I do explicitly on this site and would hate to see the site disappear? (things like my Money Routine) Well thanks to the new host I switched to in the first Updates &amp;amp; Stuff post, NearlyFreeSpeech, you can!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nearlyfreespeech.net/contribute/www.brandongiesing.com"&gt;Simply go to my Contributions page on their site&lt;/a&gt; and you can add directly to the site's funds to prevent it from going offline! They accept Credit/Debit Cards, PayPal, Dwolla, Bitcoin, and even physical checks if you mail it to them!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The site is paid daily via usage and currently only costs a couple bucks a month so even if you can only donate $5, that's still about 3 months of extra time the site can stay up! This is a great way to support the site with not a lot of money.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second method is about cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin. I previously had a button on the page that showed my Bitcoin address so you could send me some. Times have changed though since I added that when it was originally hosted on my Tumblr! Bitcoin prices are now almost at $3K and many other coins have also become popular like Ether and Monero.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To allow more coins, I've swapped the CoinWidget button with a ShapeShift Shifty Button! This will open in a new window and allow you to send me basically any altcoin you have (they support basically all) and it will get converted and deposited into my Bitcoin wallet!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="layoutupdatescontributorspageandmore"&gt;Layout Updates: Contributors Page and More!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to new ways to support me, I'm now gonna start recognizing people who have helped me (when/if somebody ever does!). There's currently nobody so the page isn't up but it will be linked in the header once somebody does!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want your name to be here, tell me who you are and 1 link you want featured (your website, YouTube, a referral, etc.) For example, people who use the new Site Fund donations I mentioned above can let me know this info in the &amp;quot;Message to Site Operator&amp;quot; box.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for other various changes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Renamed PayPal section to Cash and also added Dwolla.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Various layout improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="speedupdates"&gt;Speed Updates&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did some more optimizations on images and other things to hopefully speed up the site even more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post thumbnails have been scaled down from original sizes (4K or 1080P usually) to 720P as they show small anyway as is so the bigger sizes did nothing more but use more disk space (making the site more expensive) and slow down pages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compressed resources Ghost itself uses in addition to my personal stuff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A lot more I'm not gonna go in depth on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="cosicast"&gt;CosiCast&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id="newvideos"&gt;New Videos&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I finally released a Shorties for Glitchtale Do or Die like I've been meaning to get around to. (One on the newer episode &amp;quot;Love (Part 1)&amp;quot; is coming soon.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src="https://vid.me/e/nrew?stats=1" width="100%" height="480" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also released a Channel Trailer!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src="https://vid.me/e/DUiF?stats=1" width="100%" height="480" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;h2 id="postupdates"&gt;Post Updates&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I forgot to make posts for some of the newer videos here so I went back to make them and changed them to use &lt;a href="http://Vid.me"&gt;Vid.me&lt;/a&gt; embeds since YouTube has been having so many issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's it for this Updates &amp;amp; Stuff but stay tuned for a separate CosiCast only Edition coming very soon since I have some &lt;strong&gt;BIG&lt;/strong&gt; changes in store for CosiCast. So much more that it needs it's own post!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Ready, Set, DIE! | Glitchtale Season 2</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://vid.me/e/nrew?stats=1" width="1280" height="720" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the new episode of Glitchtale, Love Part 1, being released today, I realized I completely forgot to do my usual edit for each episode!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So for Do or Die, I decided to change things up slightly with my edit. I really tried to make it faster pace and cram&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/05/30/glitchtale-do-or-die-shorties/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">598e673cf9f83b66e1d616ba</guid><category>CosiCast Shorties</category><category>CosiCast</category><dc:creator>Brandon Giesing</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/die.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://vid.me/e/nrew?stats=1" width="1280" height="720" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/die.jpg" alt="Ready, Set, DIE! | Glitchtale Season 2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the new episode of Glitchtale, Love Part 1, being released today, I realized I completely forgot to do my usual edit for each episode!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So for Do or Die, I decided to change things up slightly with my edit. I really tried to make it faster pace and cram more stuff in to seem more action packed. My other two edits for My Sunshine and Dust were both slower paced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="credits"&gt;CREDITS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id="music"&gt;MUSIC&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vantablack (Gaster's Theme) from Glitchtale OST - NyxTheShield&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Music by NyxTheShield: &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/channel/UC9QBo6agq3a34UsiYfMtKGA"&gt;https://youtube.com/channel/UC9QBo6agq3a34UsiYfMtKGA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="clips"&gt;CLIPS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Glitchtale Season 2, Episode 3: Do or Die.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="outromusic"&gt;OUTRO MUSIC&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Energy - Michael Craig &amp;amp; Oliver Godfrey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="camilatheglitchtalecastcrew"&gt;CAMILA &amp;amp; THE GLITCHTALE CAST/CREW&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/CamiAnimations/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/CamiAnimations/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
DeviantArt: &lt;a href="http://camilaanims.deviantart.com/"&gt;http://camilaanims.deviantart.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Tumblr: &lt;a href="http://camilaart.tumblr.com/"&gt;http://camilaart.tumblr.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Twitter: @camilacuevaszu&lt;br&gt;
Twitch: &lt;a href="https://www.twitch.tv/camila2929"&gt;https://www.twitch.tv/camila2929&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Patreon: &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/camilacuevas"&gt;https://www.patreon.com/camilacuevas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strelok (Sound Designer &amp;amp; Asgore/Frisk/Kumu) - &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/carmelo580"&gt;https://youtube.com/carmelo580&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Zedrin (Sans/Gaster) - &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/ZombieZephyr"&gt;https://youtube.com/ZombieZephyr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Courtney (Betty) - &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/ProjectSNT"&gt;https://youtube.com/ProjectSNT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Jen (Jessica/Orange girl: Robin) - &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/MEMJ0123"&gt;https://youtube.com/MEMJ0123&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Adox0graphist (Asriel/Undyne) - &lt;a href="https://adoxtalks.tumblr.com/"&gt;https://adoxtalks.tumblr.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Lumisau (Green boy: Cam) - &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/lumisau"&gt;https://soundcloud.com/lumisau&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Meredith (Light-Blue Girl: Abigail): &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/Emichwan88"&gt;https://youtube.com/Emichwan88&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
KateMarie999 (Alphys) - &lt;a href="https://katemarie999.tumblr.com/"&gt;https://katemarie999.tumblr.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Citrus (Papyrus) &lt;a href="https://citrusstorm.tumblr.com/"&gt;https://citrusstorm.tumblr.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Store, Secure, Speed, Splitting, and more S words! | Updates &amp; Stuff #2</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another Update so soon! :O Yep, I've made more changes since the move to the new server so I want to make another Update post!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="newsitefeaturesandimprovements"&gt;New Site Features and Improvements!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've added a cool new thing to the site and also made some changes to make it even faster and&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/05/29/updates-2-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">598e673cf9f83b66e1d616b3</guid><category>Updates &amp; Stuff</category><category>announcements</category><dc:creator>Brandon Giesing</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 10:53:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another Update so soon! :O Yep, I've made more changes since the move to the new server so I want to make another Update post!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="newsitefeaturesandimprovements"&gt;New Site Features and Improvements!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've added a cool new thing to the site and also made some changes to make it even faster and more secure!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="cosiscommercestore"&gt;&lt;a href="https://brandongiesing.com/store"&gt;Cosi's Commerce Store&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I talk about a lot of products, I figured I would set up an AStore with Amazon where you can buy some things I like or talk about and support me in the process! It's all handled through Amazon so it's secure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="ssl"&gt;SSL!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of secure, the site now has SSL via Let's Encrypt! This will eventually allow cool new things like HTTP/2 and Service Worker that allows for the pages to load faster!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="speedoptimizations"&gt;Speed Optimizations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These sections sure flow together well! I also made many speed optimizations to the website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More images have been optimized! The biggest of which was the Dragon Maid video thumbnail which massively slowed down the home page since it was 15+ MB!! Now it and other post images have been shrunk significantly. Also, I reduced the homepage background and the avatar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've merged and modified some of the underlying Mapache theme code also. Since I only use the Purple theme variant, I merged it into the main CSS to speed up initial load times. I also made as many scripts as possible load asynchronously (aka at the same time) and deferred (aka they don't load till the rest of the page has) so you can get to the content faster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="contentupdates"&gt;Content Updates&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id="moneyroutine"&gt;&lt;a href="https://brandongiesing.com/money"&gt;Money Routine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Money Routine has been majorly overhauled! It's now split into multiple pages which should make it easier to manage, faster to update and load, and eventually allow for more detailed instructional stuff mixed in. See the Changelog on the first page for more info!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="cosicast"&gt;CosiCast&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm still working on more videos soon, just as always I have few ideas and I don't want to make something just to get something out so be patient. If any of you has ideas, please let me know! I would love to hear them!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="otherstuff"&gt;Other Stuff&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href="https://brandongiesing.com/supportme/"&gt;Support Me&lt;/a&gt; page
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coinbase Pages Discontinued&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Info about the new Store I mentioned above&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Divide sections better&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's all for now! Thanks for reading and let me know if you have any feedback on the updates below!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>New Host, Same Site | Updates &amp; Stuff #1</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the first of a series of update posts I'll be doing occasionally! This week, the site and email has been migrated to a new host&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="newhost"&gt;New Host&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've moved the site off of Ghosted and my Email off of ProtonMail. Now I'm using NearlyFreeSpeech and Gmail. Overall this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/05/22/update-1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">598e673cf9f83b66e1d616b1</guid><category>Updates &amp; Stuff</category><category>announcements</category><dc:creator>Brandon Giesing</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 01:52:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the first of a series of update posts I'll be doing occasionally! This week, the site and email has been migrated to a new host&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="newhost"&gt;New Host&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've moved the site off of Ghosted and my Email off of ProtonMail. Now I'm using NearlyFreeSpeech and Gmail. Overall this should allow me to provide the same site for way less money and have more control over it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="whyswitch"&gt;Why switch?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While Ghosted was a quick and simple way to get Ghost up and running, there was a few things that made me want to switch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The service costs $50 a year. Even though that's only $5 a month which isn't that bad for most sites, for a site that rarely has visitors like this one that's way too expensive for my needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ghosted is really slow about updating their sites to the latest version. Yes you might not want to be on the latest release ASAP to ensure the site doesn't break, I was 5 versions behind and new versions come out once or twice each month which is unacceptable due to security reasons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;While I likely won't need much stuff, since Ghosted only has Ghost, I can't setup other things without a separate host. At that point why pay for two hosts?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NearlyFreeSpeech solves the above problems:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Since it uses &lt;a href="https://www.nearlyfreespeech.net/services/pricing"&gt;&lt;em&gt;pay-as-you-go&lt;/em&gt; pricing&lt;/a&gt; and my site get's very few visitors, it should only cost about $15/year! Way less than the $50 I was paying Ghosted. (Of course, more visitors could make it more than $50 but that would be unlikely for now considering my usage)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Since I control the whole server myself, I choose when to upgrade.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can host anything I want from files, images, and other apps (things like link shortners, other CMSes like Wordpress, etc.) if I ever want to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="btn external" href="https://www.nearlyfreespeech.net/"&gt;Check out NearlyFreeSpeech&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ProtonMail meanwhile was a good encrypted email provider and is definitely more secure than Gmail but:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$48/year is overkill when you barely use email.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I rarely ever send and receive email to people, most of what I get in my inbox is newsletters and I've not had anybody who I could send encrypted messages to as is. Why pay $48/year for just newsletters and encryption you can't really use?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I would love to use some services like &lt;a href="http://Unroll.me"&gt;Unroll.me&lt;/a&gt; for instance that can't work with ProtonMail cause the very nature of its encrypted services and no IMAP/Pop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gmail on the other hand might not be as private but I do personally trust Google unlike many others and:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's free! Since my domain is through Google Domains, I get free email forwarding that also allows messages to be sent through Gmail and show up as my domain without having to pay for G Suite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Obviously, I can still encrypt messages if needed without paying the ProtonMail prices and with Gmail, I have basically unlimited storage and alias unlike ProtonMail's 5GB and 5 alias.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's Gmail which basically all email integrations work with either with Google Login or direct IMAP/POP access.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="moneyroutine"&gt;Money Routine&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the &lt;a href="http://brandongiesing.com/2017/01/23/the-nepdate/"&gt;Nepdate&lt;/a&gt;, I've split out Perk to a separate tips page like I said I would but otherwise, I've not done all I said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I split only one tips page out when I was gonna do it for most of the sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Didn't make it a full on multi-page guide&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both are still coming eventually but I have made a lot of updates since then including:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moving earnings to an auto-updating spreadsheet to update the earnings in real-time instead of after months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reducing page length via collapsing some stuff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Giving info about each and adding a lot more app types&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="otherstuff"&gt;Other Stuff&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I added the project page like I said in the &lt;a href="http://brandongiesing.com/2017/01/23/the-nepdate/"&gt;Nepdate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked on optimizing the site a lot.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compressed Images&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Modified the Mapache theme to remove some unneeded stuff and load things async-ly if possible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reduced ads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Still need to work on posting more&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's it for this update! I'm gonna continue to work on doing more stuff so stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Bendy Builders | Bendy and the Ink Machine</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I've been listening to this song a lot cause it's so freaking catchy! So I decided to edit some cool fan animations/artwork together. I didn't want to spend too much time so it's not a full blown Fan Music Video but if you guys want it, let me know&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/05/03/bendy-builders-bendy-and-the-ink-machine-shorties/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">598e673cf9f83b66e1d616b9</guid><category>CosiCast Shorties</category><category>CosiCast</category><dc:creator>Brandon Giesing</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 04:19:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/bendy.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/bendy.jpg" alt="Bendy Builders | Bendy and the Ink Machine"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I've been listening to this song a lot cause it's so freaking catchy! So I decided to edit some cool fan animations/artwork together. I didn't want to spend too much time so it's not a full blown Fan Music Video but if you guys want it, let me know and maybe I'll extend it later!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src="https://vid.me/e/yIsn?stats=1" width="1280" height="720" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;h1 id="credits"&gt;CREDITS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bendy and the Ink Machine belongs to theMeatly Games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="music"&gt;MUSIC&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Build Our Machine - DAGames &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZstsPUKT5CI"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZstsPUKT5CI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="clips"&gt;CLIPS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(If I forgot one, please let me know)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8kkCYCL_W84"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8kkCYCL_W84&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tI3Up2kzwNk"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tI3Up2kzwNk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=__bWA3qKLS4"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=__bWA3qKLS4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SnLXzG1G8NA"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SnLXzG1G8NA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tkzSF31GZwM"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tkzSF31GZwM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c_OHECDFv1Y"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c_OHECDFv1Y&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And various fan/official art found via Google Images. (again let me know if you know the exact artist)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="outromusic"&gt;OUTRO MUSIC&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Energy - Michael Craig &amp;amp; Oliver Godfrey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Jazzy Dragon Lolis | Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Maid</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://vid.me/e/WDJ4?stats=1" width="100%" height="100%" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First off, I want to say sorry for the severe lack of videos! I've either been way to busy or have no ideas when not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just recently started getting into this wonderful anime and you should check it out also! Here's an edit of some of the best clips&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/04/28/jazzy-dragon-lolis-miss-kobayashis-dragon-maid-shorties/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">598e673cf9f83b66e1d616ab</guid><category>CosiCast Shorties</category><category>CosiCast</category><dc:creator>Brandon Giesing</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 21:24:54 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/Dragons-compressor--1-.png" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://vid.me/e/WDJ4?stats=1" width="100%" height="100%" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/Dragons-compressor--1-.png" alt="Jazzy Dragon Lolis | Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Maid"&gt;&lt;p&gt;First off, I want to say sorry for the severe lack of videos! I've either been way to busy or have no ideas when not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just recently started getting into this wonderful anime and you should check it out also! Here's an edit of some of the best clips from the show so far set to an instrumental of the show's awesome, jazzy theme song!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, since I have been away so long. Enjoy a new Thumbnail Style, Outro Style and Song, and a new version of Cosi!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="credits"&gt;CREDITS&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id="music"&gt;MUSIC&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rhapsody of Blue Sky (Instrumental) - fhana (aka the Theme Song)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="clips"&gt;CLIPS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Maid&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="outromusic"&gt;OUTRO MUSIC&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Energy - Michael Craig &amp;amp; Oliver Godfrey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Launch of the Casting With Cosi Show on Anchor.fm!</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I launched a cool new variety radio show/podcast on &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm"&gt;Anchor.fm&lt;/a&gt;! Check it out at &lt;a href="http://brandongiesing.com/cwcshow"&gt;the show page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/03/24/casting-with-cosi-show-launch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">598e673cf9f83b66e1d616ad</guid><category>announcements</category><category>Casting With Cosi Show</category><dc:creator>Brandon Giesing</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 09:00:42 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/Anchor-1.png" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/Anchor-1.png" alt="Launch of the Casting With Cosi Show on Anchor.fm!"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I launched a cool new variety radio show/podcast on &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm"&gt;Anchor.fm&lt;/a&gt;! Check it out at &lt;a href="http://brandongiesing.com/cwcshow"&gt;the show page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>BrandonGiesing.com: The Nepdate!</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Funny titles aside, welcome to a new year with a new redesign for the site! Keep reading to learn about the changes or skip to the bottom for a tl;dr changelog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="whatsnew"&gt;What's New?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="theme"&gt;Theme&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The theme is changed from Caffeine by Kelvin Nguyen to Mapache by GodoFredo. Both themes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/01/23/the-nepdate/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">598e673cf9f83b66e1d616a6</guid><category>announcements</category><category>Website</category><dc:creator>Brandon Giesing</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 17:52:52 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/nepdate-1.png" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/nepdate-1.png" alt="BrandonGiesing.com: The Nepdate!"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Funny titles aside, welcome to a new year with a new redesign for the site! Keep reading to learn about the changes or skip to the bottom for a tl;dr changelog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="whatsnew"&gt;What's New?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="theme"&gt;Theme&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The theme is changed from Caffeine by Kelvin Nguyen to Mapache by GodoFredo. Both themes are good but I liked the more modern style and easier customization of Mapache.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="note"&gt;Example: Caffeine required code editing to change Social links and logo while Mapache does it with Ghost's simple Code injection making it easier to update.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also it adds some cool extras! See that fancy box above that I used for the example? That's one of the them but here's some others:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Special layouts for image and video posts
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This post is using the image layout for the giant header image.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The video layout (&lt;a href="http://brandongiesing.com/cosicast-2016-lookback/"&gt;Example here&lt;/a&gt;) adds a YouTube sub button and a play icon to the post thumbnail in addition to making the video big like the image layout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Buttons with special icons (example below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="btn external" href="https://github.com/godofredoninja/Mapache"&gt;Check out Mapache&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also like all my other social media profiles, I changed the header/cover and profile image to match. No longer does it have the wallpaper that won Nextbit's contest and my avatar with a blue background. Now enjoy the glossy Check It background and a enhanced avatar with a white background and more detail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="content"&gt;Content&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know I haven't posted much here yet but as I said in the original &amp;quot;new site&amp;quot; post, I don't have a schedule of posts and they will come at any time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That said, I do want to post more so here's a few ideas to start with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Since the theme has a video layout, I might start posting all videos as a post here like I did with the Lookback video.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I mostly did that because the description was too long for both YouTube and Vidme but it might be nice to do this as I can use it to link other sites that don't have descriptions or really short lengths to videos easier (Instagram, Coub, Twitter, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start="2"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do more review/tutorial/longform things in general.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I eat a lot of limited time food items so why not talk about them for example.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Either way, keep in mind that this is still a &amp;quot;personal website&amp;quot; and not really a &amp;quot;blog&amp;quot; so content can be anything really.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="moneyroutine"&gt;Money Routine&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, this is probably the main thing people have been here for so a few bits of info here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I update it when I feel like it. (Not every week, month, etc.) so be patient.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I'm still trying to move tips to separate pages to simplify the page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will also likely split the page up into a multi-page post and add some more tutorial like info instead of just listing stuff
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introduction and Changelog&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to get started&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Device List and Tips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earnings List&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id="newpages"&gt;New Pages&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm planning on adding more pages to the site to fill some gaps. Currently the two pages are the Money Routine and the Support Me/Donate page but there's some more that need added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;About Me/Bio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My Projects (Current/Past)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possibly others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once I do this, the old site will definitely be obsolete with everything moved over or redone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="tldrchangelog"&gt;TL;DR Changelog&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Design
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Theme: Mapache by GodoFredo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Cover: Check It Glass&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated Avatar: White background, more detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New/Updated Content
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Video Reposts from YouTube/Vidme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reviews: Food, Tech, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tutorials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Money Routine
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In Progress: Moving Tips to separate posts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not Started: Reorganize into multiple pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Pages
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;About Me/Bio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My Projects (Current/Past)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The site is currently being actively worked on so please be patient as things could be wonky, stuff missing/broken, or offline at times!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if you have ideas or an issue, let me know!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comment below&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Email me at &lt;a href="mailto:me@brandongiesing.com"&gt;me@brandongiesing.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DM on Twitter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>CosiCast 2016 Lookback</title><description>A lookback at how my video content improved in 2016.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2016/12/11/cosicast-2016-lookback/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">598e673cf9f83b66e1d616a3</guid><category>CosiCast Lookback</category><category>CosiCast</category><category>YouTube</category><dc:creator>Brandon Giesing</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 05:11:39 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/CosiCast-2016-Lookback-1.png" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/08/CosiCast-2016-Lookback-1.png" alt="CosiCast 2016 Lookback"&gt;&lt;p&gt;From all the tragedies, YouTube's crap, Trump, and more, this year has been one with many problems... However, there's been good things also including great new games, Scientific and Medical breakthroughs, and even more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, none of the above is the focus right now. Instead let's take a moment to lookback at how I've improved the video content I make! This is the 2016 Lookback at CosiCast. (formally CosiTube and before that my name)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src="https://vid.me/e/aOlO?stats=1" width="100%" height="100%" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: Not all videos of 2016 are included for a few reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some are just too big to try to edit like the Undertale Anniversary video.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;None of the videos I upload for archival purposes are included as they aren't my content. This includes things like the &lt;a href="http://Pluto.TV"&gt;Pluto.TV&lt;/a&gt; Bumpers and Election News Opens.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;None of the channel updates are included. Only the 4 main series (Shorties, Promo Promotions, In 60 Seconds, and Fan Music Videos)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Left out a few for quality reasons (either low-res or has a watermark as examples)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;None of my music as you can't hear them with the Lookback music on top so what's the point.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="timeline"&gt;Timeline&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway back to the point at hand... Let's recap how I've improved my content this year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="winterearly2016"&gt;Winter Early 2016&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early in the year I was using an editor named Adobe Premiere Clip on a BLU Energy X Plus.This was a problem for a couple of reasons... First, Premire Clip had many bugs and the videos weren't as polished. Second, that phone had little space and the app downloaded all projects (even old ones) offline and if you deleted them, you could never make changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first video of the year in January was the 3rd version of my Stamp on the Ground mashup. 1st one had just Gravity Falls, 2nd added Star vs the Forces of Evil, and the 3rd one added many other things I liked to make a &amp;quot;life mashup&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="spring2016"&gt;Spring 2016&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jump to April and I recieved early access to an Android version of an iOS only app named Replay. This was awesome as it made way fancier videos than Clip and it had less bugs. The main issue was it had a forced watermark but that was only temporary for the inital betas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first video edited with Replay was The Seven Falls FMV. Since my device was so low powered still, I couldn't use basically any of those fancy effects and was forced to use 480p footage to not crash my device. A couple of videos later with the Star vs Bad Times FMV, Replay updated making those fancy effects work better on devices like mine and removed the watermark as it got renamed to GoPro Quik which I am still using currently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="summer2016"&gt;Summer 2016&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jump to June and I started using another app by the same people as Quik called Legend to make animated text titles. The first use was in the Stranger in the Stars FMV. This video was also the first I made a custom thumbnail for which I made in MediBang! Paint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later that month was the launch of Pravox VARIETY and a shit in my videos. I started to do less comedy or music mashups and instead do more promos for either creators or Pravox VARIETY itself. This was when I made the first &amp;quot;Now on Pravox&amp;quot; promos which evolved into Promo Promotions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="fall2016"&gt;Fall 2016&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jump to September and this is when a big shift occured! First I got a new phone (the Nextbit Robin) so I could finally used 1080p footage with no issues or render bugs. Second, I introduced the first of the 4 series with the Turbo Flowers FMV! Before this I just called most of my videos &amp;quot;Mashups&amp;quot; but their was two distinct styles of Mashups so I split it into both FMVs and Short Edits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the start of October, I launched the second of the 4 series, In 60 Seconds, with the Google Phones video for the Pixel launch. Later that month, I renamed Short Edits to Shorties and also combined the Fan Promos and Pravox PRESENTS promos into Promo Promotions as I shut Pravox Networks down due to nobody using it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was also around the time I switched from using my name (Brandon Giesing) to CosiTube as the channel name to give it a brand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="winterlate2016"&gt;Winter Late 2016&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, we are now at the end of November with the Hyperdimension Neptunia Shorties! This is when I started to not just improve the content itself but how my content is viewed!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of my content (so excluding archival stuff) now will have custom thumbnails following a consistent template (made in Canva) with Cosi on an outlined quarter-circle in the corner, each show has a logo that appears on that thumbnail, titles follow a consistent format (&amp;quot;Video Name | What it's based on | Series Name&amp;quot;), and lastly an outro with music and end cards to go to the latest video or others from that series.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also I decided to change the name again from CosiTube to CosiCast to make it less &amp;quot;YouTube-focused&amp;quot;. Alongside this, I started using other sites alongside YouTube including &lt;a href="http://Vid.me"&gt;Vid.me&lt;/a&gt; as a mirror for videos (in case #WTFU strikes), Coub, Instagram, Twitter, and Rabadaba for video previews and even sometimes Early Access.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So this year has been great for my content and I hope next year will be even better! So what's coming next year? Well I don't know for sure yet but here's some ideas!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doing more of the current 4 series (especially In 60 Seconds as I haven't done many of them) which is a no-brainer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possibly try another attempt a weekly or bi-weekly series like The Weekly Prime.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expand the content I base from. Currently I'm basically in a bubble of Gravity Falls, Star vs., Undertale/Glitchtale, Creators (like The8BitDrummer, Lost Pause, etc), and Neptunia but with a limited pool to pick from, I run out of ideas easily.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possible new series that aren't scheduled (like the current 4). One idea I've had for a while is &amp;quot;React Recap&amp;quot; where unlike traditional &amp;quot;Blind Reactions&amp;quot; I would analyze a video and points made by other reactors. (So for instance say I did one on the Glitchtale S2 premiere... Many people were speculating on who the shadowy figure was at the end (Spoiler: it was Betty). I would have gave my thoughts on who it could be and why while also discussing what the other reactors have speculated and why their points could be true.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Either way, thank you guys (and girls) so much for watching my content! While I rarely get comments so I don't know how many people actually watch, if you do I'm glad you keep coming back for more. I hope you have a great holiday season!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>1st Month of Money Making | My Earnings and What I Do</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;EDIT: &lt;a href="http://brandongiesing.com/money/"&gt;See my new dedicated money page for constantly updated info!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So today is September 21st (in Missouri/Central Time Zone) and on August 24th, I started using &amp;quot;Beer Money&amp;quot; apps. So while it's not the end of the September for a monthly roundup kind of post, it's&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2016/09/21/1st-month-earnings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">598e673cf9f83b66e1d616a2</guid><dc:creator>Brandon Giesing</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 06:03:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;EDIT: &lt;a href="http://brandongiesing.com/money/"&gt;See my new dedicated money page for constantly updated info!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So today is September 21st (in Missouri/Central Time Zone) and on August 24th, I started using &amp;quot;Beer Money&amp;quot; apps. So while it's not the end of the September for a monthly roundup kind of post, it's the end of my first 4 weeks of money making so I figured I would write a bit about it! My earnings, my devices, what apps/sites, and more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: I have no job because very few people want to hire an autistic teen who has weight, sight, sleep, and knee issues. So I'm here doing this all day and most likely make more than you would.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="mydevices"&gt;My Devices&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far I use 5 dedicated mobile devices, my main phone, and 2 PCs for money making. I also bought a Google OnHub to improve my internet this past weekend with ~$200 of birthday money.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="mobiledevices"&gt;Mobile Devices&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Nexus 7 (2012)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Nexus 7 (2013)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moto E (2015)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LG Optimus Zone 3 (first device bought for Money making)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BLU Energy X Plus (was main up till Monday)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nextbit Robin (main device, got it Monday after winning a contest)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="pcs"&gt;PCs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acer Aspire Z All-in-one Desktop running Windows 10&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TOSHIBA C55t Laptop with CloudReady (aka Chrome OS, Neverware makes it working with Google mostly for Schools to use it without upgrading old computers)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id="myappsandroutine"&gt;My Apps and Routine&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don't have any set schedule of what devices should be doing what at certain times but here's the basics of what I do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If they are linked, it's my referral link! Otherwise, just search for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.swagbucks.com/refer/dotmaniac39"&gt;Swagbucks (Web+Apps)&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run as many of the Swagbucks apps as I can. Some days only SBTV and Lifestylez on 2 devices since they often give me non-stop bonus rounds but sometimes I do the rest also, usually max 3 devices (The 2013 Nexus and BLU for 2, my Robin also if 3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ToolbarTV/Swagbutton videos is always running on my Laptop. Since it now works passively, it's just always there while I'm doing other stuff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Swag codes and Inbox videos also if I remember them or they are not expired by time I get to them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagc.com/bgiesing"&gt;InstaGC (Web)&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watch section running on desktop 24/7 unless Playlist runs out while asleep.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://perk.fm/4utfk"&gt;Perk (Apps)&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perk TV is always running on the LG Optimus and Moto E 24/7. The BLU joins it overnight since Swagbucks is always messing up with the ads and the Nexus 7 (2012) joins after running...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AppTrailers runs on my Nexus 7 (2012) before turning on PTV and I convert the points to Perk. Also run though it on my Nextbit Robin and the BLU.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use Viggle occasionally but rarely watch TV&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://Perk.tv"&gt;Perk.tv&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://Viggle.tv"&gt;Viggle.tv&lt;/a&gt; get used some but they run like crap on my computers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Checkpoints (Apps)
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Runs on Nexus 7 (2012) overnight because what I said above under Perk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First check in to the one business that appears nearby my house and then I play all the videos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S'more and SlideJoy (Apps)
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lockscreen apps that pay each time you unlock your screen. Only use on my main (was BLU, now Robin)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Rewards [formally Bing Rewards] (Web)
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search with Bing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run Microsoft Edge for the browse and earn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete Dashboard tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EarnHoney (Web)
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ran the videos, don't anymore as the site is really prone to crashing my computers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, I run use Rabadaba, Foap, and &lt;a href="http://Flii.by"&gt;Flii.by&lt;/a&gt; which pays for making posts. I haven't got anything yet so they aren't in the earnings below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've also tried some others but either couldn't get them to work or they take way to long. This includes Inbox Dollars, GiftHulk, and a few more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="myearnings"&gt;My Earnings&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So of course this is what you really want to know, right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also only Swagbucks has been since Day 1 so not all apps have had their full potential yet. Bing Rewards and the Lockscreens were started before Aug. 24th but I only started them regularly, non-stop 4 weeks ago with Swagbucks, I will include all-time earnings for those and only this months since the others are all all-time earnings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that said, here's my earnings this month:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Swagbucks: 6019 SB or $60.19&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;InstaGC: 1,938 Points or $19.38&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perk/AppTrailers/Viggle: 8,595 Perk Points or ~$8.60&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Checkpoints: 784 points or ~$1.20&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S'more:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All-time since May 15th, every day except 5/23-6/29 as I forgot to reinstall when phone got reset: 955 points or $9.55&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This month: 270 points or $2.70&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SlideJoy:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All time since October 2015 (can't remember exact date). Again every day except when I forgot to reinstall sometime between December 2015 and March 2016: $16 (their point values have changed since I started so don't have points for this one)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This month: 2,943 SlideJoy Carats or $2.94&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft/Bing Rewards
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All time, on and off since May 2014. Everyday since August 24th: 15,740 Microsoft Points aka 1574 Bing Credits before the rebrand or ~$15 for 2 Amazon gift cards, 1 Windows Store card, and 50 points donation to my old school.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This month: 7240 Microsoft Points or 1 $5 Amazon Gift Cards and 3240 points left to another one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total:&lt;/strong&gt; ~$100.01 (some values might be slightly off like the Microsoft Rewards as they are harder to calculate but at least $100, possibly higher by a couple bucks or so)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of that is merely from what I mentioned above! No referral earnings on any of them except InstaGC which 34.75 of the 1,938 is referrals (so not even a full dollar as 100=$1).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Welcome to the new BrandonGiesing.com!</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;So if you know me, I have a &amp;quot;habit&amp;quot; of constantly moving my site cause &amp;quot;reasons&amp;quot;. This time, hopefully this will be permanent now that I got great software and money to keep it alive!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="greatsoftwareghost"&gt;Great Software: Ghost&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the past I have done many different&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2016/09/19/welcome-to-the-new-site/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">598e673cf9f83b66e1d616b0</guid><dc:creator>Brandon Giesing</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 10:01:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;So if you know me, I have a &amp;quot;habit&amp;quot; of constantly moving my site cause &amp;quot;reasons&amp;quot;. This time, hopefully this will be permanent now that I got great software and money to keep it alive!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="greatsoftwareghost"&gt;Great Software: Ghost&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the past I have done many different CMS, Blog, and Static services for my sites. Wordpress, Blogger, Weebly, Webs, and even Tumblr are some of those many.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another one I used is Jekyll. I used it more than the others as it's static (aka fast) and can be freely hosted via GitHub Pages. While this is nice, one big issue is Mobile publishing. Git on phones is not the easiest to do and managing the site became an issue but of course, I'm not going back to the other ones as while they have great mobile tools, many of them are really slow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I'm using &lt;a href="https://ghost.org"&gt;Ghost&lt;/a&gt; which is different in a few ways!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Node.js (instead of PHP) means it's faster like Static pages but still with the interactivity of CMS platforms like Wordpress.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use Markdown just like most Static sites like Jekyll.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No mobile app but the website is mobile-friendly and it's open source with an API so there's awesome 3rd-party clients like Quill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The major issue with Ghost though has to do with that first point some...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="letstalkaboutthe"&gt;Let's Talk About The $$$&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PHP has lots of hosts that are free. (Yes they maybe really limited but for a simple personal site with rarely any views, not a big deal) Node.js however basically has none. Heroku and OpenShift exists but are super complicated to set up or can't run newer versions easily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just under a month ago (August 24th, 2016 to be exact) I started doing some money sites. Yeah, I know you are going to say &amp;quot;They are scams aren't they?&amp;quot; (Not all are) or &amp;quot;Those things can't pay out enough for a server&amp;quot;. Well you would be right normally for the second point except 1 key detail... I have no job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That means I'm at home 24/7 doing these but what's even better is I'm not really doing anything! All the ones I use are passive video apps. This means I open it up, let it run on my old devices, and forget it. (Well mostly, sometimes there's a broken ad that needs manually closed but otherwise all automatic). On average for just 1 of the 3 main ones I use (and I do experiment with others), I get on average $3 a day. Add the other 2 sites and each does about $2 on average. So $7 just for having videos run while I'm doing other things!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How much does hosting Ghost cost? Well for that...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="ghosthostghostedit"&gt;Ghost Host: &lt;a href="http://Ghosted.it"&gt;Ghosted.it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ghosted.it"&gt;Ghosted.it&lt;/a&gt; is an interesting host made specifically for Ghost! They cost $5 a month which is really inexpensive for web hosting at $60 per year. However if you buy that full year, it's 20% off at only $50. In not even a full month with those sites (and the few others outside the main 3), I've redeemed around $55 and have another $25 I can cash out in a few days on only the one site! I already spent most of that initial $55 for phone stuff on Amazon but still, I can get the $50 pretty fast!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://Ghosted.it"&gt;Ghosted.it&lt;/a&gt; manages the server and everything for you so all I have to do is make the content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="aboutthenewsite"&gt;About The New Site&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that all that is out of the way... What about my side of it? The content? Well here's how the site is going to work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occasionally I post long-form content here about things I'm interested in. Whether it be about tech products, talking about new food items, or anything else, if it needs lots of words, it will most likely be here.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I'll share links to them on existing social accounts like my Twitter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Want to find info about my projects? I'll have dedicated pages in the Menu. Currently I have a &amp;quot;Support Me&amp;quot; page where you can find ways to support me via donations or using my referral links.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More may happen but the main thing is unlike my past personal sites, &lt;strong&gt;I will not do a scheduled post series!&lt;/strong&gt; I always forget about them or don't have enough things to make one each week! So I may do post series but they won't be &amp;quot;Every Sunday&amp;quot; or something, just when I get to them!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The site is currently being actively worked on so please be patient as things could be wonky, stuff missing/broken, or offline at times! So for the meantime, you can find the old website at &lt;a href="http://old.brandongiesing.com"&gt;http://old.brandongiesing.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please tell me any feedback by commenting below with Disqus or emailing me at &lt;a href="mailto:me@brandongiesing.com"&gt;me@brandongiesing.com&lt;/a&gt;! Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>